<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Cleodora Forecasting</title><link>https://cleodora.org/</link><description>Recent content in About on Cleodora Forecasting</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cleodora.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/use-cases/</guid><description>Use Cases # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
Some examples how Cleodora could be used.
Mindy the engineer # Mindy is an engineer who works at a company that just hired a new CEO on January 1st 2022. She predicts he will leave the company by the end of the year.
Mindy makes the following forecast on January 2nd 2022:</description></item><item><title>Roadmap &amp; Requirements</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/roadmap/</guid><description>Roadmap &amp;amp; Requirements # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
Version 1 # The MVP (Minimal Viable Product) must implement the following features.
Web-based Make binary (yes/no) forecasts (title, description, probability of being true 0 - 100, datetime, reason for probability, closing date) Edit forecast. Modify title, description and closing date Update prediction. Allow modifying the probability 0 - 100 and attach a datetime to it.</description></item><item><title>Comparison with other tools</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</guid><description>Comparison with other tools # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
Cleodora is different from Manifold Markets because:
Running it locally on your computer will be the default and all forecasts are private whereas, on Manifold everything is public Cleodora is about your own forecasts, not other people&amp;rsquo;s You can directly measure the quality of your forecasts instead of only indirectly via the amount of M$ (mana) you earn over time, meaning you can better drill down where exactly you failed in specific instances Cleodora is different from Metaculus because:</description></item><item><title>Dev Guidelines</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/dev-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/dev-guidelines/</guid><description>Dev Guidelines # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
The following should be prioritized, in particular over feature completeness:
Long-term maintainability, including a high degree of automation and tests Easy setup and excellent &amp;lsquo;Getting Started&amp;rsquo; documentation for new contributors Simplicity of use Personal use and privacy When in doubt, new features will not be added.</description></item><item><title>Technology</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/technology/</guid><description>Technology # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
I have a vague idea that the combination of a Go backend with a ReactJS frontend could work well.
Go makes it easy to create a single binary for different platforms I personally like Go React seems to be very popular and battle-tested If using Go, then Gin could be a good choice as a framework.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/contributing/</guid><description>Contributing # If you think you can help, please get in touch!
Contact: info@cleodora.org
GitHub: https://github.com/cleodora-forecasting/cleodora</description></item><item><title>FAQ - Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/faq/</guid><description>FAQ - Frequently Asked Questions # Why care about forecasting? # Forecasting is an important skill. Essentially all decisions we take are based on vague gut-level predictions. For example before leaving for the airport you predict how much the traffic will delay you on your way, timing your departure appropriately. You also make a prediction about how likely you think it is your car will suffer a catastrophic engine failure on the road.</description></item></channel></rss>