<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Cleodora Forecasting</title><link>https://cleodora.org/</link><description>Recent content in About on Cleodora Forecasting</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cleodora.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/use-cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/use-cases/</guid><description>Use Cases # Some examples how Cleodora could be used.
Mindy the engineer # Mindy is an engineer who works at a company that just hired a new CEO on January 1st 2022. She predicts he will leave the company by the end of the year.
Mindy makes the following forecast on January 2nd 2022:
Will Tom, our new CEO, leave the company by December 31st 2022? Prediction: Yes Confidence: 60% Reasoning: His track record shows that he switched companies 8 times in the last 10 years and I have a bad gut feeling about him.</description></item><item><title>Comparison with other tools</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</guid><description>Comparison with other tools # Manifold Markets # Cleodora is different from Manifold Markets because:
Running it locally on your computer will be the default and all forecasts are private whereas, on Manifold everything is public. Cleodora is about your own forecasts, not other people&amp;rsquo;s. You can directly measure the quality of your forecasts instead of only indirectly via the amount of M$ (mana) you earn over time, meaning you can better drill down where exactly you failed in specific instances.</description></item><item><title>Contact &amp; Feedback</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/contact/</guid><description>Contact &amp;amp; Feedback # Feedback and suggestions are very welcome!
Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).</description></item><item><title>FAQ - Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/faq/</guid><description>FAQ - Frequently Asked Questions # Why care about forecasting? # Forecasting is an important skill. Essentially all decisions we take are based on vague gut-level predictions. For example before leaving for the airport you predict how much the traffic will delay you on your way, timing your departure appropriately. You also make a prediction about how likely you think it is your car will suffer a catastrophic engine failure on the road.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/credits/</guid><description> Credits # &amp;lsquo;External link&amp;rsquo; icon, used in the menu, free with attribution from flaticon.com</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog # All notable changes to this project will be documented in this file.
The format is based on Keep a Changelog, and this project adheres to Semantic Versioning.
Unreleased # Git history
0.1.0 # Added # cleosrv application that runs a local webserver on Windows, Linux or MacOS Docker image cleodora to run cleosrv cleoc CLI (command line interface) application to interact with a cleosrv server GraphQL API that allows listing forecasts and associated outcomes and probabilities List forecasts, outcomes and probabilities in the web frontend included in cleosrv Create new forecasts with associated outcomes and probabilities via cleoc Create new forecasts with associated outcomes and probabilities via the web frontend included in cleosrv Git history</description></item></channel></rss>