<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Cleodora Forecasting</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Cleodora Forecasting</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cleodora.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comparison with other tools</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/comparison/</guid><description> Comparison with other tools # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
Cleodora is for personal predictions, not for aggregating data of multiple people Cleodora is for tracking your own performance and systematically improving it With Manifold Markets your performance is hidden with all the other ways of getting mana plus there is no easy way to measure whether you are improving or which areas you need to work on With Metaculus only certain kinds of general interest predictions are allowed, not personal ones Privacy is important so self-deployment is the default</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/contributing/</guid><description>Contributing # If you think you can help, please get in touch!
Contact: info@cleodora.org
GitHub: https://github.com/cleodora-forecasting/cleodora</description></item><item><title>Dev Guidelines</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/dev-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/dev-guidelines/</guid><description>Dev Guidelines # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
The following should be prioritized, in particular over feature completeness:
Long-term maintainability, including a high degree of automation and tests Easy setup and excellent &amp;lsquo;Getting Started&amp;rsquo; documentation for new contributors Simplicity of use Personal use and privacy When in doubt, new features will not be added.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/roadmap/</guid><description>Roadmap # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
Version 1 # The MVP (Minimal Viable Product) must implement the following features.
Web-based Make binary (yes/no) predictions (title, description, probability of being true 0 - 100, datetime, reason for probability, resolution date) Edit question. Modify prediction title, description and resolution date Update prediction. Allow modifying the probability 0 - 100 and attach a datetime to it.</description></item><item><title>Technology</title><link>https://cleodora.org/docs/technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cleodora.org/docs/technology/</guid><description>Technology # Everything is a work in progress. Feedback and suggestions are very welcome! Open a ticket on GitHub or send an e-mail (info@cleodora.org).
I have a vague idea that the combination of a Go backend with a ReactJS frontend could work well.
Go makes it easy to create a single binary for different platforms I personally like Go React seems to be very popular and battle-tested If using Go, then Gin could be a good choice as a framework.</description></item></channel></rss>